<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Panagiotis Skarlas</title>
  
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="https://pskarlas.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2017-03-12T15:43:58.000Z</updated>
  <id>https://pskarlas.github.io/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Panagiotis Skarlas</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Why i decided to learn Software Development</title>
    <link href="https://pskarlas.github.io/2017/03/12/Why-i-decided-to-learn-software-development/"/>
    <id>https://pskarlas.github.io/2017/03/12/Why-i-decided-to-learn-software-development/</id>
    <published>2017-03-12T15:30:47.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-03-12T15:43:58.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Intro"><a href="#Intro" class="headerlink" title="Intro"></a>Intro</h2><p>I’ll start off by saying that Programming/Software development is a form of art. It is a highly creative process that blends in analytical and problem solving skills with a strong “no-quit” mindset.</p>
<h3 id="Am-i-curious"><a href="#Am-i-curious" class="headerlink" title="Am i curious?"></a>Am i curious?</h3><p>It all started when i was browsing web apps couple of years back and i was curious, asking myself “How can they do that?” or “How does that work?”. This curiosity led me to find out the ‘how’, try to dive deeper and understand, and as you can guess the only way i could accomplish that was through start learning about software development. I began making small steps by building small websites and thats when i understood that i take a really serious joy in programming! Why? Because i become a craftsman, an artist who can take hard logic and use it creatively to produce something unique and often intriguing. </p>
<h3 id="Creativity"><a href="#Creativity" class="headerlink" title="Creativity"></a>Creativity</h3><p>Creativity, the root of Software Development, matters a lot to me, is what makes my life fun and is what gets me excited each and everyday when i wake up in the morning. Software development simply embraces creativity, it is truly a creative problem itself. So what more could i ask for? i simply decided to get serious about software development and start the process of never-ending learning.</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;h2 id=&quot;Intro&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Intro&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;Intro&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ll start off by saying that Programming/Software develop
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
